Guide to the David M. Kennedy Papers SC1115
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Personal, Professional & Administrative, Series 1
  - Valazquez, Jorge (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - World Wars Essay (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Quantification - Richard White (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Yosemite (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Wirth, John (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - N.E.H. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - National Humanities Institute (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - OAH - Denver; "Progressivism: Overview", 1974 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Kennedy - CV (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Kennedy - Stanford Professional Files (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - David Kennedy's Development Stuff (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - History Department (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - David Kennedy's GROUP (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Offer Letters (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Progressivism (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - "American People" Series (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - American Studies (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Fellowships, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - AIRF II (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Professional Journalism Fellowships, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Italy (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Gary Hart (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - "The Great War, The Last Battle," by Tom Weidlinger (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Personal (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Personal (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Research Files, Series 2
  - Research Notecards (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Japanese Surrender (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Bomb (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Troops: Culture, etc. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Ch. 22 - writing notes (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - WWII - Misc (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - WWII/Pacific - Notes (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - WWII Misc (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ch. 2 - Notes (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Chapter 3 - Notes (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Ch. 4 Notes (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ch. 5 Notes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Strategy: Mediterranean & No. Africa (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Unconditional Surrender (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - WWII General (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 17 - Notes - Unready Ally, Uneasy Alliance (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - IX. WWII Determs. of Am. Strategy (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Epilogue (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Air War (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Book: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - WWII: Europe - Notes (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - European War - Endgame (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - New Deal: Labor (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Court Fight - notes (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture - Notes (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Prologue - Notes (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Ch. 1 - notes (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - WWII Domestic - Notes (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - WTBT: Bibliographies (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - US in WWII - General (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "Cauldron of Homefront" - notes General (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "Cauldron" - Writing Notes (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Blacks in Wartime (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bracero Program (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - WWII Women (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Misc. - Book (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - New Deal: Retrospect (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Japanese Internment (& Italians) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Culture/Values - WWII (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - South in War (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - West in WWII (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Politics - WWII (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Misc Notes (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Newspapers (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Freedom from Fear
    - Freedom From Fear: Prologue (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 2 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 3 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 4 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 5 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 5 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 5 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 6 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 6 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 7 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 8 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 9 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 9 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 10 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 10 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 11 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 11 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 12 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 12 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 14 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Freedom From Fear: Chapter 21 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Prologue - Chapter 3 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Chapter 4 - 7 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Chapter 8 - 11 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Chapter 12 - 15 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Chapter 16 - 18 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Freedom From Fear Penultimate Master: Chapter 19 - end (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Freedom From Fear, Final Master: Prologue - Chapter 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Freedom From Fear, Final Master: Chapter 6 - 10 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Freedom From Fear, Final Master: Chapter 11 - 14 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Freedom From Fear, Final Master: Chapter 15 - 17 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Freedom From Fear, Final Master: Chapter 18 - end (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Pageant (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Map Transparencies to Accompany Bailey/Kennedy THE AMERICAN PAGEANT (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Map Transparencies to Accompany Bailey/Kennedy THE AMERICAN PAGEANT (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Map Transparencies - The American Pageant (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Assessment of Research-Doctorate Programs (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hist 165C: The United Staets in the 20th Century - Course Reader (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Great Depression: World War II and the American West (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Reconstruction (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Economy (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Oil (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - For. Econ. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Post-WWI; International Political Economy (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Finance (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Shipping (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - For. Econ. Post-War Planning Policy (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - BR. Post-War Trade (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Econ (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Paris Econ. Conf. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Notecards A (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Notecards B (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Notecards C (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Notecards D (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Notecards E (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Notecards F (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Notecards G (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Notecards P (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Notecards R (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Notecards S (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Notecards T (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Notecards U (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Notecards V (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Notecards W (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Notecards L (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Notecards M (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Notecards Mc (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Notecards N (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - World War I: U.S. Entry (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Wilson and War: diplomacy (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Wilson and Peace Treaty (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - American Diplomacy, Civil War and after (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - US and Russian Revolution (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Labor: Late 19th century (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Woodrow Wilson: Pre-Presidential (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Watergate (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Election of 1952 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Progressive Party: 1912 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Taft: "insurgency" (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - 1920s: Historiography (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Productivity and Efficiency: 1920s (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Labor and Agric: 1920s (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Business and Public Policy: 1920s (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Election of 1896 and late 19th century political culture (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Theodore Roosevelt: biography (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - TR: foreign policy (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Agriculture: Late 19th century (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - World War II: war-time diplomacy (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - ETS 1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - European Imperialism, late 19th century (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Northwestern (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Personal Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - University Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Personal Correspondence (Spring 1994) (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - University Correspondence (Spring 1994) (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - "Personal Corresp" (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Personal Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Kennedy, David (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Graduate Research Seminar 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Research Seminar 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Modern America, 1997-98 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dept. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - History 153, 1987-88. "Grt. Dep., New Deal, and WWII" (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - West (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Coe Workshop, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Enemies" (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pageant (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Grad. Research Seminar, '96-'97 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Committments, 1996-97 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - WWII Research Seminar (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - AP Inst., Stanford July 10, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - AP Institute, Utah - Aug. 14, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Yale (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Chit-Chat (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Suri (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Karen Sawislak: Tenure Reviews (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Oklahoma (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - History 165C, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Houghton-Mifflin (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Seminar 1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Atlantic (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Revision Notes - Misc (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Revisions: General (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Revisions: General (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Research (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 8: The Rumble of Discontent (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Prologue: Rev. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Ch. 1 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Ch. 2 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ch. 3 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Ch. 4 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Ch. 4 - Rev. - Part II (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 5 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ch. 6 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Ch. 7 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 8 - Rev. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Freedom From Fear (?) complete draft, unfoldered but in opened shrinkwrap. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Research Notecards (Box 20)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 1-7 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 1-7 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 8-12 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 8-12 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 13-21 (1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 13-21 (2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Freedom From Fear: Draft - Chapters 13-21 (3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - News clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - US - Canada: Comparisons and Interrelations Conference, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, from "The Atlantic", 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Photography, by Stanford News Service (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Writing (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - David Kennedy's Publications and Publication Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - CV (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Personal (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Personal (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Germany, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Chapter 9 (Part II) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Chapter 9 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Chapter 10 (inc.) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Chapter 11 "To The Brink" (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Pac War Rev. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Freedom From Fear: Revisions - Eur. War Rev. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 18, Revisions, Part II (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 18 Girding for War (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 18 - ex: Mark Brilliant (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 17 - Unready Ally, Uneasy Alliance (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 21 "Cauldron" (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 22 - Revisions (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Freedom From Fear: Epilogue (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Freedom From Fear: Ch. 18 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Research Notecards - Birth Control (Box 25)
  - Birth Control in America - Draft MSS (1 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Birth Control in America - Draft MSS (2 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Birth Control in America - Draft MSS (3 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Birth Control in America - Draft MSS (4 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Birth Control in America - Draft MSS (5 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Research Notecards - Over Here (Box 28)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS & Notes - Ch. 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Over Here - Source and Data Check (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Over Here - Ch. II - Rough Copy (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Over Here - Ch. One (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Over Here - Draft MSS (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Over Here - WWI: Final Phase (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Over Here - Notes (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Preparedness (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - World War I - General Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - World War I - Correspondence with Publishers (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - World War I (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - World War I (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - World War I (Box 36)
  - World War I - Travel Aid (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - League (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Churches (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - World War I (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - World War I Bibliography (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Canada (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - World War I - State Councils (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Politics (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pacific Northwest Quarterly, 1968 Oct (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 3 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 4 - Over There (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - General (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - General Notes (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Intellectuals (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Intellectuals (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Prologue (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Book Research (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - World War I - Library of Congress (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - World War I - Library of Congress - Labor (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - World War I - Library of Congress (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - World War I - Trade (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - World War I - Library of Congress (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Draft - Political Economy Chapter (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Draft/Notes - Chapter 3 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Draft - Various Chapters (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Teaching, Series 3
  - Custom Course Pack Misc & Syllabi (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Course Reader: Hist 165C America in the 20th Century, Spring 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pubs - Book of the Month Club "Views" & "The Stanford Historian" (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Splendid Little Accidental War? Accidental War Theory and 1898, by Rob Rakove. Honors Thesis, Stanford History Department. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Course Reader: History 165C, America in the 20th Century, Spring 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Course Reader: Hist 259A, Strategy and Statecraft: Theory and PRactice from the Eighteenth Century to the Present, Spring 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Course Reader: Hist 128, The Second World War in Europe and America, Winter 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Coe Workshop: The United States in Depression and War, 1929-1945. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Course Reader: IHUM 026B, Democratic Society in Europe and America, Spring 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Course Reader: Hist 165C, America in the 20th Century, Spring 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - OAH, 1986 (NYC) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hist 258 - "Modern America" Winter, 1990-1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Seminar, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hist 271S - Undergrad Seminar "War & Society" (Winter, 1975) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - History 165C, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hist 258S: Winter, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Room Information, Stanford (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - History/American Studies Search (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Interactive Education (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Virginia - Digital History (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coe Summer Seminar, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - HI104 - US His Course Notebook (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hist 351E, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - History 3 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - History 3, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Course Eval. Stevens - Spring '04 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Coe Workshop 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AHA - 1989 - SFO (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 4th of July Op-Ed (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "West" Conference 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Panel - 10/21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AP Conf - Stanford. July 17-18, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dept - Review/visit (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Catton Prize Committee (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bookstore (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Teaching Atlantic History" - Harvard, '98 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - OAH - moderator (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Prog. on Contemp. Polit. History (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Spring Course Evaluations - Sheehan, Spring (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Course Evaluation spring '02 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Course Eval Spring '00 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - OAH 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Immigration Seminar, '92-93 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - History 351C, Spring 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 351C 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hist 174 - "Am. Cond." 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Syllabi: History 351C (Joint Grad. Colloq.) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - David's class materials 84-85 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Condition in 20th Century 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 165C - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Hist. 351E - Jt. Grd. Colloq. Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - History 351F - Spring 1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Am. Condition - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Jt. Grad. Colloq. - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - history 258: "Mod. Am. in Historical Perspective" Spring '88 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hist. 165C: 20th-C. US 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Hist. 351 - Spring 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Cold War (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Conservation (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Family History (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Feminism (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Film (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy (general) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Historiography (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Japanese-Americans (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - John F. Kennedy (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Literature (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Individualism (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Intellectual History (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Immigration (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - New Deal (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Progressive Era - MSS (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Race Relations (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Reprints (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Socialism and the Left (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Southern History (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Supreme Court (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Urban Studies (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Western History (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Women (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - World War I (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - World War II (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - US History Search (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - W. Cultures (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mammarella (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cliveden Program, 1980 Summer (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - America in Western Civ. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - History Correspondence (Kennedy) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - David Kennedy's Personal Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Professional Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Professional Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - History 174 "American Condition" 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Critiques, Hist. 171, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy - Seminars (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - American Condition, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Pageant - 8th Edition (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pageant - 7th Edition (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pageant - 6th Edition (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Joint Grad. Colloq., 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - History 165c - Spring, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Joint Grad. Colloq., 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Grad. Research Seminar - History 456, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Triumph (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Travel Study
    - S. Pacific College, SAA Travel Study, 1991 Sep 1-19 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - S. Pacific College, SAA Travel Study, 1991 Sep 1-19 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Suitcase Seminar (England and France), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Thailand (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Tuscany (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Tuscany (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Venice, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Stanford in Washington, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Stanford in Washington, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Intracoastal Waterway, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Yosemite (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - America in Western Civilization - Italy, 1976-1977aw (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reciprocal Vision (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Hum. 195 - "America in Western Civilization", 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - History 174 - American Condition in 20th Century (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "American Condition", 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Econ. Hist. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Syllabi: Graduate History (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Syllabi: History 170 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Syllabi: History 171 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Syllabi: History Undergrad Seminars (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Syllabi: Humanities Honors Seminar (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "America in Western Civ." Winter, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - WWI - Grad. Seminar (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Syllabi: Others (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Syllabi: History 156 (Social Thought) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - History 165c, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - PJF Seminar, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - American Studies Seminar (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Seminar: Biography, Autobiography, History (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - "La Tradizione Politica Americana" (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Grad Research Seminar - WWI Era, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - History 165c, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - History 165c (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - History 165c - Spring, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - History 169S: Winter, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - History 266s-Fall Quarter, U.G. Sem: U.S. Foreign Policy, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - History 266s, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - History 455A - Grad. Seminar. Winter., 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - History 174/English 128 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 2005 Spring (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Course Reader: IHUM 026A - Democratic Society in Europe and America, 2000 Winter (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 1997 Spring (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 2001 Spring (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 1995 Spring (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 1998 Spring (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Course Reader: IHUM 026A - Democratic Society in Europe and America, 2001 Winter (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Course Reader: History 165C - The United States in the Twentieth Century. Professor David M. Kennedy, 1999 Spring (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Society in Europe and America, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Research Seminar 456B Spring '02 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - WWII Seminar 1998 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - History 28 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - WWII: Section (96-97) (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - History 165C-2002 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - History 165C-2000 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Hist 165C - 1994 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Jt. Grad. Colloq, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 43)